{
  "questions":[
    {
      "question": "What is JSON?",
      "answers": [
        "website",
        "a popular means of transferring data between servers and clients",
        "Journalistic Stream Of News",
        "teacher name"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "0",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 'Singleton'?",
      "answers": [
        "Common name for Non-functional requirements",
        "a software design pattern that restricts the instantiation of a class to one object",
        "a software design pattern that restricts the instantiation of a class to limited number of object",
        "Common name for Domain requirements"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "3",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    },
     {
      "question": "test driven developments includes?",
      "answers": [
          "Software Testing",
        "Regression Testing",
        "Maintenance Testing",
         "Code Testing"
     	],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    }, 
     {
      "question": "'Factory method', 'Strategy' and 'Adapter' are 3 kinds of:",
      "answers": [
         "Cloud srevices",
        "functional Requirements",
        "agile methods",
         "Design Patterns"
     	],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    }, 
    {
      "question": "In testing process: what comes first?",
      "answers": [
         "Release testing",
        "Development",
        "User testing" 
     	],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    }, 
     {
      "question": "Tools that used for unit testing?",
      "answers": [
         "draw.io",
        "JUnit",
        "Xampp",
         "Visual Paradigm"
     	],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "0",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    }, 
    {
      "question": "before you release your product to  real use she needs to pass the tests of",
      "answers": [
        "Software Testing",
        "Release Testing",
        "Maintenance Testing",
        "Code Testing"
     	],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "0",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    },
     {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a 'Private cloud' advantage?",
      "answers": [
        "High level of security",
        "Customizable ",
        "High performance",
        "Low cost"
     	],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    },
   {
      "question": "'Windows Azure', 'Heruko' and 'force.com' are examples for:",
      "answers": [
        "IaaS",
        "SaaS ",
        "PaaS",
        "BaaS"
     	],
      "correct_ans": "3",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    },
    {
      "question": "tool for version control is?",
      "answers": [
        "big bucket",
        "Turrent",
        "visual paradigm",
        "draw.io"
     	],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "0",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a feature of a good software?",
      "answers": [
        "stand alone system",
        "entertainment",
        "effiency",
        "have a nice font"
     	],
      "correct_ans": "3",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following roles is not described as a core role in 'Scrum'?",
      "answers": [
        "Product owner",
        "Team",
        "Product owner",
        "architect"
     	],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    },
    {
      "question": "UML Diagrams types includes one of the following diagrams:",
      "answers": [
        "Petri Net",
        "BPMN",
        "DSD",
        "StateChart"
     	],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    },
    {
      "question": "UML Diagrams types includes one of the following diagrams:",
      "answers": [
        "Petri Net",
        "BPMN",
        "DSD",
        "StateChart"
     	],
      "correct_ans": "4",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "hedgehog"
    }
  ]
}